<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Generated by crowdin.com-->
<resources>
  <string name="conditions_text_long"><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><html><head></head><body><b>FINARX Single Use License</b><br/>
<br/>

By downloading, installing or using this application, any future versions, updates, substitutions, or copies made by or for you (collectively, the \"Application\"), you agree to be bound by the following Terms and Conditions (the Terms). If you disagree with any of these Terms, do not use the Application, FINARX GmbH and its owners, members, directors, and managers (collectively, \"FINARX\") does not grant you the license and right to install or use this Application.<br/>
<br/>
FINARX reserves the right to update and change, from time to time, these Terms without notice to you. You can always find the most recent version of these Terms at http://www.finarx.eu/agbs.pdf. You understand and agree that your use of the Application after such change constitutes acceptance of such changes.<br/>
<br/>
1. USE OF THE APPLICATION<br/>
<br/>
The Application is owned by FINARX.  FINARX grants you the non-exclusive, non-transferable, non-sublicenseable, limited right and license to install and use the Application solely and exclusively for your use under these Terms. The Application is licensed, not sold. All rights not expressly granted to you are reserved by FINARX.<br/>
<br/>
a. You may download, install, personally use and run one (1) copy of the Application on a single personal mobile or personal computing device that you own or control at any one time and may use the Application for your own personal, non-commercial use or benefit.<br/> 
b. If you are a commercial enterprise or educational institute, you may download, install, use and run one (1) copy of the Application for use either: (a) by a single individual on each mobile or computing device that you own or control at any one time, or (b) by multiple individuals, one at a time serially, on a single mobile or computing device that you own or control.<br/> 
c. You understand that you use the Application (or servers or networks which are connected to the Application) at your own risk.<br/>
d. You agree to use the Application only for purposes that are permitted by (i) these Terms and (ii) any applicable law, regulation or generally accepted practices or guidelines in the relevant jurisdictions (including any laws regarding the export of data or software to and from the United States or other relevant countries).  These laws include (but are not limited to) restrictions on destinations, end users and end use.<br/>
e. You agree that you are solely responsible for (and that FINARX has no responsibility to you or to any third party for) your use of the Application, any breach of your obligations under these Terms, and for the consequences (including any loss or damage which FINARX may suffer) of any such breach.<br/>
f. You may not use the Application in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, disrupt or impair the Application (or servers or networks which are connected to the Application), nor may you use the Application in any manner that could interfere with any other party\'s use and enjoyment of the Application (or servers or networks which are connected to the Application).<br/>



g. You may not use the Application in any unlawful manner, for any unlawful purpose, or in any manner inconsistent with these Terms.<br/>
h. You may not use the Application in any manner where human life or property may be at stake. You understand that the Application is not designed for such purposes and that its failure in such cases could lead to death, personal injury, or severe property or environmental damage for which FINARX is not responsible.<br/>
i. You may not use, or export the Application in violation of applicable U.S., german and E.U. laws or regulations.<br/>
<br/>
2. PROPRIETARY RIGHTS<br/>
<br/>
The Application is protected by copyrights, trademarks, service marks, international treaties, and/or other proprietary rights and laws of the U.S. and other countries.  You agree to abide by all applicable proprietary rights laws and other laws, as well as any additional copyright notices or restrictions contained in these Terms.  These Terms grant you no right, title, or interest in any intellectual property owned by FINARX, including (but not limited to) the Application and FINARX trademarks, and creates no relationship between yourself and FINARX.<br/>
<br/>
a. You acknowledge and agree that FINARX owns all legal right, title and interest in and to the Application, including any intellectual property rights which subsist in the Application (whether those rights happen to be registered or not, and wherever in the world those rights may exist).<br/>
b. You agree that you will not, and will not allow any third party to, (i) modify, decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble or otherwise attempt to derive source code from the Application or content that may be presented or accessed through the Application for any purpose unless otherwise permitted, or create derivative works (as defined by the U.S. Copyright Act) or improvements (as defined by U.S. patent law) from the Application or any portion thereof, (ii) sell, rent, lease, loan, distribute, transfer, reproduce, copy, trade, resell or sublicense the Application or access thereto or derive income from the use or provision of the Application, whether for direct commercial or monetary gain or otherwise, without FINARX\'s prior, express, written permission, (iii) use the Application to access, copy, transfer, transcode or retransmit content in violation of any law or third party rights, or (iv) remove, obscure, or alter FINARX\'s or any third party\'s copyright notices, trademarks, or other proprietary rights notices affixed to or contained within or accessed in conjunction with or through the Application.<br/>
c. Unless you have agreed otherwise in writing with FINARX, nothing in these Terms gives you a right to use any of FINARX\'s trade names, trade marks, service marks, logos, domain names, and other distinctive brand features.<br/>
<br/>
3. FEATURES AND SUPPORT<br/>
<br/>
FINARX may elect to provide you with customer support and/or software updates, upgrades, enhancements, or modifications for the Application (collectively, \"Support\"), in its sole discretion, and may terminate such Support at any time without prior notice to you.  FINARX may change, suspend, or stop (permanently or temporarily) any aspect of the Application at any time.  The Application may also impose limits on certain features and services or restrict your access to parts or all of the Application without notice or liability.<br/>
<br/>
You may stop using the Application at any time. You do not need to specifically inform FINARX when you stop using the Application.<br/>
<br/>
4. TERMINATION<br/>
<br/>
Your right and license to the Application under these Terms continue until they are terminated by either you or FINARX as set forth below.  In such events, you must immediately discontinue the use of and permanently delete the Application.<br/>
<br/>
a. You may terminate these Terms at any time by discontinuing the use of and permanently deleting the Application in its entirety.<br/>
b. These Terms terminate automatically without notice from FINARX if you violate any of these Terms.<br/>  
c. FINARX may at any time, terminate these Terms by posting a written notice of termination online, or FINARX sends a written notice of termination to you.<br/>  
<br/>
5. YOUR PRIVACY<br/>
<br/>
a. FINARX\'s privacy policy is available at http://www.finarx.eu/privacy. This policy explains how FINARX treats your personal information, and protects your privacy, when you use the Application.<br/>
b. You agree to the use of your data in accordance with FINARX\'s privacy policies.<br/>
<br/>
6. FEES AND PAYMENTS<br/>
<br/>
a. FINARX reserves the right to charge fees for future use of the Application in FINARX\'s sole discretion. If FINARX decides to charge for the Application, such charges will be disclosed to you prior.<br/>
b. Unless otherwise provided by law, all charges are earned when received and are nonrefundable, and the costs of any returns will be at your expense.<br/>
<br/>
7. CONTENT IN APPLICATION<br/>
<br/>
You understand that all information such as data files, written text, computer software, music, audio files or other sounds, photographs, videos or other images (collectively, \"Content\") which you may have access to as part of, or through your use of, the Application are the sole responsibility of the person from which such content originated.<br/> 
<br/>
a. You understand that by using the Application you may be exposed to Content that you may find offensive, indecent or objectionable and that, in this respect, you use the Application at your own risk.<br/>
b. You agree that you are solely responsible for (and that FINARX has no responsibility to you or to any third party for) any Content that you create, transmit or display while using the Application and for the consequences of your actions (including any loss or damage which FINARX may suffer) by doing so.<br/>
<br/>
8. U.S. GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS<br/>
<br/>
This Application, related materials and documentation have been developed entirely with private funds.  If the user of the Application is an agency, department, employee, or other entity of the U.S. Government, the use, duplication, reproduction, release, modification, disclosure, or transfer of the Application, including technical data or manuals, is restricted by these Terms.  In accordance with Federal Acquisition Regulation 12.212 for civilian agencies and Defense Federal Acquisition Regulation Supplement 227.7202 for military agencies, use of the Application is further restricted by these Terms.<br/>
<br/>
9. INDEMNIFICATION<br/>
<br/>
To the maximum extent permitted by law, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless FINARX, its affiliates and their respective owners, members, directors, officers, managers, employees and agents from and against any and all claims, demands, actions, suits or proceedings, as well as any and all losses, liabilities, damages, costs, and expenses (including reasonable attorneys\' fees) arising out of or accruing from your use of the Application, including your downloading, installation, your violation of any of these Terms, your violation of applicable laws, or your violation of any rights of another person or entity.<br/>
<br/>
10. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES<br/>
<br/>
YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE APPLICATION, ANY DATA OR CONTENT ACCESSED THROUGH THE APPLICATION, AND SERVERS OR NETWORKS WHICH ARE CONNECTED TO THE APPLICATION IS AT YOUR SOLE DISCRETION AND RISK.  THEY ARE PROVIDED \"AS IS\" AND \"AS AVAILABLE\" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.<br/>
<br/>
YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR MOBILE DEVICE, COMPUTER SYSTEM, OR OTHER DEVICE, OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM SUCH USE.<br/>
<br/>
FINARX EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, RELATING TO THE APPLICATION AND ANY DATA OR CONTENT ACCESSED THEREFROM, OR THE ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, COMPLETENESS, RELIABILITY, SECURITY, FUNCTIONALITY, OR ADEQUACY OF THE APPLICATION AND ANY DATA OR CONTENT ACCESSED THEREFROM, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.<br/>
<br/>
THE APPLICATION IS NOT DESIGNED, INTENDED OR LICENSED FOR USE IN HAZARDOUS ENVIRONMENTS REQUIRING FAIL-SAFE CONTROLS, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE DESIGN, CONSTRUCTION, MAINTENANCE OR OPERATION OF NUCLEAR FACILITIES, EMERGENCY COMMUNICATIONS, AIRCRAFT NAVIGATION OR COMMUNICATION SYSTEMS, AIR TRAFFIC CONTROL SYSTEMS, LIFE SUPPORT OR WEAPONS SYSTEMS, OR ANY OTHER ACTIVITIES IN WHICH THE FAILURE OF THE APPLICATION COULD LEAD TO DEATH, PERSONAL INJURY, OR SEVERE PHYSICAL OR ENVIRONMENTAL DAMAGE.  FINARX SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR SUCH PURPOSES.<br/>
<br/>
IF THE APPLICATION, ANY DATA OR CONTENT ACCESSED THROUGH THE APPLICATION, AND SERVERS OR NETWORKS WHICH ARE CONNECTED TO THE APPLICATION PROVE DEFECTIVE, YOU (AND NOT FINARX) ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL REPAIR OR INJURY OF ANY KIND, EVEN IF FINARX OR ITS REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF OR SHOULD HAVE BEEN AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH A DEFECT OR DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW RESTRICTIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES SO SOME OF THESE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.<br/>
<br/>
11. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY<br/>
<br/>
YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT FINARX, ITS SUBSIDIARIES AND AFFILIATES, AND ITS LICENSORS ARE NOT LIABLE TO YOU UNDER ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY FOR ANY AND ALL DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES THAT MAY BE INCURRED BY YOU OR BY THIRD PARTIES, THROUGH THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE OR ACCESS THE APPLICATION, ANY DATA OR CONTENT ACCESSED THROUGH THE APPLICATION, AND SERVERS OR NETWORKS WHICH ARE CONNECTED TO THE APPLICATION, INCLUDING (BUT NOT LIMITED TO) ANY LOSS OF DATA OR DAMAGE TO YOUR MOBILE DEVICE, COMPUTER SYSTEM, OR OTHER DEVICE, ANY LOSS OF PROFIT (WHETHER INCURRED DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY), ANY LOSS OF USE, ANY LOSS OF GOODWILL AND REPUTATION, OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSS, WHETHER OR NOT FINARX OR ITS REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF OR SHOULD HAVE BEEN AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY SUCH LOSSES ARISING.<br/>
<br/>
12. ADVERTISEMENTS<br/>
<br/>
The Application is supported by advertising revenue and may display advertisements and promotions. These advertisements may be targeted to the content of information stored by the Application or other information.  The manner, mode and extent of advertising by FINARX are subject to change without notice to you.<br/>
<br/>
You agree that the Application may display such advertising to you.<br/>
<br/>
13. GENERAL LEGAL TERMS<br/>
<br/>
a. These Terms constitute the entire understanding and the whole legal agreement between you and FINARX and govern your use of the Application, superseding, and completely replace all prior or contemporaneous agreements between you and FINARX regarding the Application.<br/>
b. You agree that the failure of FINARX to exercise or enforce any legal right or provision of these Terms shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision and that those rights or provision will still be available to FINARX.  If any court of law of competent jurisdiction rules that any provision of these Terms to be invalid, then that provision will be removed from these Terms without affecting the rest of these Terms. The remaining provisions of these Terms will continue to be valid and enforceable.<br/>
c. These Terms, and the relationship between you and FINARX under these Terms, shall be governed by the laws of the State of California without regard to its conflict of law provisions. You and FINARX agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located within the county of Santa Clara, California to resolve any legal matter arising from these Terms.  Notwithstanding this, you agree that FINARX shall still be allowed to apply for injunctive relief (or an equivalent type of urgent legal relief) in any jurisdiction.<br/>
<br/>
14. SURVIVING PROVISIONS<br/>

<br/>
Sections 1 through 3, 5 through 11, 13 through 14, and those that by their terms apply after termination of this agreement will survive any termination of this agreement.</string>
</body></html>]]></string>
</resources>
